(Recap)
Guess we'll head back together.
No problem.
(Date Day)
There will be a boy and a girl.
Two chances
(Sun Qimeng invites Zhao Xilun)
for the Courageous.
(Zhao Xilun invites Sha Yue'er)
It always follows
(The sunflower always follows the sun)
the sun.
That's
the Courageous' flower?
It's a flower the Courageous gave you.
(The flower for you)
I really didn't expect someone
to be brave
(I didn't expect that)
for me.
Their relationship
is definitely heating up.
Yeah.
Chen Hewen.
Go for it.
Cool.
(First stargazing room date invitation)
I always thought I'd like
someone more reserved.
But now I'm realizing
being direct is pretty great too.
He fell for it.
The sky is falling.
Let's have your favorite
Combo A tomorrow.
Does he want to join too?
Going straight for it.
"♪Don't stay trapped inside your room♪
♪Outside the window,
the rain has cleared♪
♪Set reality aside♪
♪Follow your heart♪
♪What you've been longing
for is right ahead♪
♪Don't act like you didn't see it♪
♪Just be a little braver♪
♪Come closer, come closer♪
♪There's a little spark
shining in your eyes♪
♪That's the signal
of a heart coming alive♪
of a heart coming alive♪"
=Heart Signal (China Version) S9=
We're here.
Here we are.
Good to see you again.
Welcome
to WeTV's
sweetest
social observation reality show,
Heart Signal.
We're now on Season 9!
This program
is exclusively sponsored
by Master Kong Sugar-Free Jasmine Tea.
Every sip is as fragrant
as the first blossom.
Join us for a cup of fine tea.
Pantene Peach Hair Care.
Summer hair, made better.
Fresh repair, light as air.
Special thanks to Pantene
for sponsoring the show.
The innovative smart SUV, AITO M6.
Your ride to romance.
Ready to take you wherever life leads.
Build your Heart Signal.
Make every date a new surprise.
This program
is sponsored
by the LEGO Botanicals Collection.
Crispy, crunchy, oh so good!
More fun with Oreo.
This program
is sponsored by Oreo.
OLAY Chinese Valentine's Day Gift Set
Limited-edition merch.
Hydrating essence, toner & lotion.
Everything you need in one set.
Treat yourself or your bestie.
Give it to someone you love.
Downy In-Wash Scent Beads.
Fresh fragrance all day long.
Never lose that spark.
Thanks to Downy for sponsoring.
Xizhilang Plum Jelly.
Only you, always you.
An official sponsor
of Heart Signal
Season 9.
It's
a new week.
First,
let's welcome
JinZhao couple.
(JinZhao couple)
We're
JinZhao couple
from Heart Signal Season 6.
I'm Lucky Zhang.
I'm Zeng Zhaohao.
Zeng Zhaohao.
(JinZhao married couple)
Well...
I guess we're the married couple now.
(Caught off guard)
Happy newlywed life!
I was just about to ask.
(A little dazzling)
So shiny!
Is there anything you want to ask?
I have a question.
I heard
(Cupid Du Haitao)
you couldn't wait
to get married
after proposing.
But you couldn't even
book a venue.
Right.
We didn't realize until later
(Guest Cupid Zeng Zhaohao)
that the venue
was the first thing
we needed to book.
Now,
you basically have
(Wedding venues need early booking)
to book one a year
to a year and a half in advance.
The venue got you.
The venue held you up.
Yeah, the venue held you back.
(Happy problem)
Welcome, you two!
So happy.
Come on, let's look back
at the heart-fluttering
moments
and memorable scenes
from the past week.
That ending.
(Chen Hewen, Sha Yue'er)
They were having a great conversation,
and then suddenly,
Zhao Xilun
walked in.
(Zhao Xilun)
I think he was tying his shoe.
Wasn't he?
Was it this scene?
He didn't go there
to tie his shoe.
He was trying to leave,
and then he bumped into a table.
I was really curious about what happened
after he went downstairs.
We were all curious.
Me too.
That one moment
felt straight out of a TV drama.
Yeah.
They were chatting downstairs,
while someone
was standing by the window.
(So cinematic)
Look, that day,
we were wondering
what would happen to Sun Bohan.
(Sun Bohan)
But look
what happened next.
Turns out
- he was really handsome.
- That broad-shouldered.
Yeah, he used to look so cool.
But then, in the end,
he was wearing
a white shirt,
and the collar was already all wrinkled.
And loose.
He was grilling barbecue, right?
And then Cui Kaiyi
and Cao Yiheng, right?
(Cui Kaiyi, Cao Yiheng)
Did they actually go to Tianjin?
You're really worried about that.
You've basically got
a three-minute recap.
(Three-minute recap
of Heart Signal Season 9)
Seriously,
I think
our storyline
is really intense and fast-paced.
Things
are moving so fast.
The pace is really fast.
Way too fast.
And
(Chen Hewen invited Sha Yue'er)
the stargazing room is coming up.
That thing with Chen Hewen.
Yeah.
They were outside.
That doesn't count
as the stargazing room.
No, he was trying to get into the room.
He never made it inside.
He got caught outside.
Yeah.
He got caught.
Come on.
Let's see
how everyone's
love lines
have changed
this week
after their first date.
Come on!
Let's go.
Let's see what new stories
unfold this week.
Here we go.
(Episode 3: Where Stars Meet the Moon)
For example, on the first day
when we were in the same room,
I felt like you barely looked at me.
How could that be?
I thought...
(Turns around)
He couldn't feel anything anymore.
(Opens door)
Love is pain relief.
So, at first sight...
He's coming.
Hi, guys.
Hello.
(Takes a glance)
Hi, you're back.
Hi.
Zhao Xilun is here.
I saw a flash of light
just now.
So I came out
and saw you guys talking.
(Stargazing room invitation card)
He saw the invitation card.
(Looks)
(Steps back)
He shouldn't be here.
He should be under the car.
He should be under the couch.
Would he go back
for a Master Kong Jasmine Coin?
I'll go. Then I'll be the next.
He should put one in too.
Yeah, I actually wanted to...
(Crosses arms)
I actually wanted
to apologize.
I was worried you might be hungry
because you hadn't eaten anything.
(Didn't get dinner on the date)
Their date only lasted half a day.
Maybe I should give you two
some privacy.
It's okay.
Yeah, you guys talk first.
I'll just...
(Chooses to leave)
That's fine.
It's okay.
Bye. See you later.
Bye.
Bye bye.
Then you...
We went to make slime.
That's really fun.
(Cupid Dai Xu)
He wanted to apologize.
Yeah.
He was watching.
Zhao Xilun couldn't
stop thinking
about not taking
Sha Yue'er out
for a meal.
He felt bad about it.
That back view...
(Looks)
(Checks the rule board)
He's replaying everything
that happened today.
He's studying the rules.
(Check-in rules)
Oh no. He must be regretting it now.
Why didn't I do that?
He has a lot on his mind.
(Looks again)
Keeps looking at it.
Did you guys eat enough today?
Yeah, we're full.
Today was the day we ate the most
since coming to the Signal House.
Yeah.
It was all inside the tent.
Smells so good.
(Looks)
Meng.
Yeah, Meng.
This one...
The shrimp are so good.
(Invites)
Come have one.
Smells so good.
This is really good.
So good.
It's cheese-flavored.
Yeah.
They added butter.
Smells so good.
Did you eat it?
You already finished it.
Meng kept watching
Zhao Xilun's reaction.
It's okay. Just put it here.
That's all I have. I mean, you...
You're washing dishes again?
(Paces around)
Maybe I should do it.
I don't really have anything to do.
Si, you can take a break.
It's okay. I'll wash these.
Give me this one
after you finish washing it.
I didn't use this one.
I'll just put it back.
Okay.
He needs something to do.
He needs to keep busy
so he doesn't overthink.
Is the water getting blocked?
Yeah.
Aren't you done washing?
I'm done.
I'm just washing my hands.
(Sun Qimeng)
Why is this exactly like
what happens in dramas?
It's so realistic.
Art comes from life and rises above it.
Can friends with broken hearts
come to my house and do chores?
(Cleaning service)
The "Heartbreak Cleaning Service".
(Spots him)
It's okay. Sun Bohan is still here.
(Walks over to Zhao Xilun)
What's wrong?
There was a projection outside.
A projection?
You should go take a look.
It's really beautiful.
Now I'm curious what projection it is.
It's one of those
multimedia projections.
Oh my God.
Oh my.
It's actually the sky.
Oh my God.
Oh my.
Look, who's that?
Who is that? I can't see clearly.
Hi.
Everyone noticed it.
So romantic.
- You blushed again.
- I told you, you should go.
Now I'm blushing again.
Sun Bohan looked even more worn out.
All over again.
What did you do today?
You two...
We took the same car
and drove around Qianmen
and Tiananmen all day.
(Left the kitchen)
One person's mood
affects another person's mood.
I saw it.
Well,
I was curious
about what exactly triggers the canopy.
I mean, what activates the canopy?
He must've used a stargazing card.
Shouldn't it have happened
inside the stargazing room?
Yeah.
Why did it happen outside?
Maybe he used today's card
and then used tomorrow's,
or one for a day with good weather.
That makes sense.
They're on the same page.
Look.
Wanna talk for a bit?
Let's go.
Let's talk.
Let's talk for a bit.
They're both in the same situation.
How was your day today?
It was pretty good.
Pretty good.
Just some good friends hanging out.
You guys went to Daxing for barbecue?
Why did Sha Yue'er come back so late?
Well, Chen Hewen ran into her
when she came back
just now.
He stole her away.
Why didn't she come back with you guys?
I went out
with Sha Yue'er first this afternoon.
My original plan for our date
wasn't just to do a craft.
Of course, we had to grab dinner.
So I wanted to wait for her to come back
and apologize to her.
I might've seemed a little rude earlier.
(Zhao Xilun)
I'm a little...
He feels a little guilty
and a little frustrated now.
So how did you feel
about the vibe between you
and Sha Yue'er today?
I actually felt pretty...
How should I put it?
I was happy,
but I just
don't know how to put it.
We had a great conversation.
But she...
She kept smiling too.
I felt like she was happy.
But I think she's very composed.
All I can say is she doesn't dislike me.
But whether she likes me or not,
I really can't tell.
He's feeling a little unsure now.
The reason I chose to be the Courageous
was that I felt like
the four of us
really clicked yesterday.
Meng,
you sounded amazing today.
You sounded great too.
Honestly, I was so embarrassed.
But seriously,
you really sounded like Teresa Teng.
You really sounded
just like the original singer.
You have such great control
over your voice.
Your soft mix was really good.
Thank you.
I actually had
a bad feeling yesterday.
(Bad feeling)
Because I feel like a girl
with her personality,
who's so open and straightforward,
might just see me
as a good friend.
So I thought,
I needed to let her know
how I felt.
So I decided to be the Courageous.
I think once you choose
to be the Courageous,
you shouldn't worry about the outcome.
(Don't worry about the outcome)
If you're going to be the Courageous
and you like her,
(Sun Bohan)
just go for it.
Liking someone
isn't something
you need to be shy
or embarrassed about.
If you like her, just go for it.
(Be open about your feelings)
You have to accept
that other people can openly
show their interest in Sha Yue'er.
Yeah.
Well said.
And don't worry
that she might only
see you as a friend.
The moment you start thinking that way,
your whole mindset
will change.
Your behavior and actions
will be affected by her behavior
and everything the people
who like her do.
You'll let all of it
affect your emotions,
and you'll just wear yourself out.
Right.
Yeah.
So what if she just sees you
as a friend?
Be open about how you feel
about her.
Let her know how you feel.
That's enough.
Exactly.
Who she finds more attractive
is up to her.
You said
exactly what I needed to hear.
So, who do you...
Who do you most want to get to know?
He knows how to ask.
Stop hitting me where it hurts.
It's hard to say. There's no "most".
If I had to pick one...
Because I feel like
the person I've spent the most time with
is probably...
It's Sha Yue'er.
He's too embarrassed to say it.
He's comforting
and encouraging his rival.
His reaction is hilarious.
His mouth is wide open.
I haven't really spent much time
with the others, you know.
Then why don't you make a move?
He's a late bloomer.
Well, I...
Now it's his turn.
He's not saying anything.
(Yeah)
He can't get the words out.
My situation is complicated.
Actually, I'm kind of a...
(How should I put it?)
Soft-hearted person.
Because I feel like you and...
He still has his reservations.
But in my opinion,
it's like you just said.
Just be open and straightforward.
Yeah, that's what I want to do.
But I always feel like...
But then you're the one
who gets hurt.
I can understand that.
Because there's no rule saying
anyone has to do anything.
Because I support you.
I just support
whatever you want to do.
(I support you doing what you want)
That's very honest.
Yeah.
Face your true feelings.
That's really nice.
Zhao Xilun is pretty interesting.
He knows they both
like the same girl.
I'll support
whatever you want to do.
I actually have
a bit of Sun Bohan's mindset in me.
I'm not
the type
to keep pushing
when I like a girl.
I might give her some space.
Sun Bohan said
he's soft-hearted.
When he said that,
I saw him
in a new light.
I think
when he goes
after a girl,
he feels like
he'd be hurting another guy.
So if someone else
is coming on strong,
he might choose
to just sit back and watch.
But he still holds on to his feelings.
He just won't keep pushing
(Cupid Yang Chaoyue)
and make things feel
even more pressured.
He's definitely a good guy.
That really elevated their relationship.
Even though
his face
looked pretty grim,
but I think
he was glowing
on the inside.
One thing I find interesting
is that
an opponent and an enemy
aren't the same thing.
With an enemy,
there's usually a winner and a loser.
(Expert Sami)
But an opponent can sometimes
make you think more deeply
about your own role
and where you stand.
So their fair competition
and interactions here
(Fair love. Respect either way)
are pretty clear.
Fiona, in your everyday life,
are you the one who gives advice,
or the one who needs friends
to give you advice?
I...
(I don't give specific advice)
I don't give them advice.
When I do give advice,
I'm not looking at it
from a girl's perspective,
nor am I looking at it
from a guy's perspective.
I look at it
from the perspective
of what's best
for the relationship.
I will
look at
what their problem is
and then help him (her)
find the happiest version
of himself (herself).
(There's something to that)
You...
You're like a therapist.
(Healing hearts)
I feel healed.
I think when you're in love,
you don't just love that person.
Sometimes,
(Seeing yourself through them)
you see a part
of yourself in them.
(Absolutely agree)
Exactly.
That's so true.
That is so true.
Then you'll always
stay by his (her) side,
but deep down,
you don't love him (her) that much.
I don't think he (she)
wants you to be
that kind of person either.
So there's no trick.
No move can be the best move.
Just look at JinZhao.
(Just look at JinZhao couple)
Look at you.
Actually,
Sun Bohan and Zhao Xilun
are the same.
For example,
even though their relationship
hasn't even started yet,
look at them.
The way
they talk about it.
Maybe I know I'm lacking
a little courage right now.
If he can
understand all this
by the end of tonight,
that would be perfect.
Right.
Knowing isn't enough. You have to act.
(The advice we give)
I think every time we advise someone,
(is often meant for us too)
we've told ourselves the same thing.
Right.
(Agreed)
(Cao Yiheng and Cui Kaiyi
return to the Signal House)
That's so pretty.
Let's go.
Go.
Here.
After you.
The romantic "couple" is back.
Someone's chatting.
Let's hear the gossip
I'm loving this.
Hello.
So romantic.
Everything just got brighter.
Keep going.
We won't interrupt.
Bye bye.
Your outfits match so well today.
You two both look so good.
Go.
Let's go.
Careful.
I walked onto the grass.
I was too busy watching them.
She's so cute.
Cui Kaiyi is hilarious.
This lamp.
It's so pretty.
I like flowers too.
Hello.
Hi.
What time did you guys get back?
We got back around eleven too.
You just got back too.
Yeah.
Go upstairs and change your shoes.
I'll go up first.
I totally forgot.
I'll go up first
and come back down later.
They match so well.
(They both placed theirs by the bed)
They really click.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I didn't sleep well last night.
At least I can get
some good sleep tonight.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Back to the room.
Where did you just go?
I went to ask someone out.
The three of them are here.
One bedroom.
All like the same person.
How can they possibly sleep at night?
I don't know why.
I just couldn't sleep peacefully.
Yeah.
Stargazing date.
I pressed that button.
Then the light came on.
Some are happy, some are worried.
So basically,
you used the Master Kong Jasmine Coin.
I just used one.
I figured
it's been sitting there for days,
and no one had used it.
The way he said that
sounded pretty smug, huh?
I figured
it's been sitting there for days,
and no one had used it.
(Asking)
Why weren't you in the stargazing room?
Why were you outside?
Maybe you have to book it in advance?
(Follow-up question)
What's the process?
There's actually one on the left
and one on the right.
So once you press them,
something pops up right away?
(Slowly rising)
How do you choose then?
Do you just say who you want to choose?
Or...
No.
Because I didn't really
understand the rules.
You can actually go find her
and give her that thing.
(I see)
We can only use it once a week.
Is it within seven days,
or is it based on...
I think the once-a-week one
is the city date.
But the stargazing room
should be available every day.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
(Moving to a single room)
I'll sleep in that room tonight.
Okay.
Because I have something very important
tomorrow.
Yeah.
Okay.
Look, he doesn't dare sleep
in this room anymore.
He's probably afraid
they'll keep an eye on him.
(Well?)
These two.
They're about to get started.
The besties.
How was your...
(Stargazing card)
Chen Hewen?
Yeah.
So what happened yesterday?
(Curious)
Yesterday,
Liang Xiaoyu texted Chen Hewen.
They cleared up the misunderstanding.
I'm mad.
What kind of guy is he?
Men
are like clothes.
So cute.
Cui Kaiyi is so cute.
I just forgive him a little.
So we misunderstood him yesterday.
We misunderstood him.
And we spent all that time analyzing it.
Who would've thought it'd be this?
She's so happy.
Happy. She's genuinely happy.
I'm kneeling again.
You're completely different
from yesterday.
Yesterday,
as soon as you came in, you were like,
"What does he mean?"
"I'm really mad."
And today, you came in and just knelt.
Knelt.
Then you started laughing.
I give up.
No.
I should calm down a little.
Stay calm.
(Self-soothing)
I'm actually not bothered at all.
You know?
(As if I'd believe you)
What?
(Gets up)
What's wrong?
Is there a bug?
No, I was checking myself out.
Why am I blushing?
Feeling pretty good, huh?
Wonder if it's
The Courageous
or the stargazing card that did it.
She's a smart one.
Please. You made me blush.
I did?
Yeah.
I blush every time I see you.
Okay, I'll take your word for it.
Oh, so that's what happened.
I kind of misunderstood him yesterday.
I feel bad.
I don't feel bad.
I do.
You sure don't.
These two are hilarious.
I feel bad.
This is too funny.
She had him all wrong.
Cui Kaiyi is seriously the best friend ever.
Absolutely.
I just remembered one I can play.
Let me try it again.
Okay.
This place is so artsy.
Wait, don't play yet.
I wanna hear about your date today.
Well...
The scenery was actually really nice.
And the guy was great.
But Beijing traffic was awful,
so I got a little
carsick.
(Laughs)
I mean...
You went at the worst time
for traffic in Beijing, right?
Mine was pretty funny too.
Our boat ride
wasn't quite what I expected either.
It was a kayak, so we had
to face each other and paddle like this.
And the water kept splashing us.
The funniest part is,
before I came here,
I said I wasn't into looks.
Then I got here
and completely proved myself wrong.
I said I didn't care
what someone looked like,
and then I saw him
and completely folded.
Love at first sight.
She just loved his face.
I have a question.
Rank the guys by how handsome they are.
Sure.
Let's hear it.
This'll be fun.
Come on.
Honestly, I think Zhao Xilun is the hottest.
(Zhao Xilun is the hottest)
And then...
Let me think about all the guys.
I miss
our time at the house.
Did you rank us back then?
No.
(Desperately avoiding the question)
(I don't believe her)
She definitely did.
Number one is
Zeng Zhaohao.
(Number one)
I believe you.
And then...
Let me think about all the guys.
Sun Bohan.
He's number...
Two.
So the top two are tied?
No. Only Zhao Xilun
is number one.
(Only Zhao Xilun is number one)
Only Zhao Xilun is number one.
He is exactly her type.
Nothing we can do about that.
Seriously, nothing we can do.
Okay. Zhao Xilun first, Sun Bohan second.
Okay. Congrats to him.
You know
what was
hilarious on the way back?
He was so tired,
he fell asleep.
And I looked over and thought,
"Wow, he's so handsome."
You know,
when he looks like that,
especially from the side,
he's so handsome.
It doesn't matter what he's doing.
As long as he's easy on the eyes.
Exactly.
(Guest Cupid: Zhang Jin)
I think so many
of Meng's
little mannerisms are adorable.
Especially when she first
wanted to show Zhao Xilun how she felt.
She hid inside
and cheered herself on.
- Yeah, I thought that was so cute.
- Come on. Be brave.
What about you?
Who's your type?
Okay, let me think.
I think my taste is a little weird.
Zhao Xilun is
definitely handsome.
Objectively, he's very handsome.
But he's not really my type.
(Chen Hewen ranks higher)
I might put Hewen higher.
Then Cui Yihang.
But honestly, I don't think
either of them is that handsome.
I just think I like...
Guys with smaller eyes?
I get it.
(Like guys with smaller eyes)
I totally get what you mean.
Guys with smaller eyes.
Yeah, I get that too.
Thanks.
So you don't have
a preference between those two?
If I had to choose,
I'd put Chen Hewen first.
(Chen Hewen is number one)
Chen Hewen goes first?
Everyone really
does have different tastes.
It's basically the small-eyes camp
vs. the big-eyes camp.
(Packing)
(Chen Hewen moves into a single room)
(Humming)
♪Love is sweeter than honey♪
Love really is sweeter than honey.
You could tell from that little moment
just now
that Liang Xiaoyu
still has a thing
(Liang Xiaoyu & Chen Hewen)
for Chen Hewen.
Yeah.
Even though
she just
went on a date
with Cui Yihang
today,
you can see
where her heart is leaning.
When we were at Signal House,
I thought the girls'
conversations
were really
interesting.
It took me right back to school,
like hanging out in the dorm.
Sharing all that stuff was so much fun.
You know how
one day you're like,
"How could he do that?"
And the next day you're like,
"Oh, I totally misunderstood him."
That's exactly
what happened with Sha Yue'er.
(Cupid: Zhang Chunye)
From Sha Yue'er
and Cui Kaiyi's conversation,
I think Cui Kaiyi is a wise one.
(Cui Kaiyi, the wise one)
She seems
carefree and easygoing,
but every word she says hits the mark.
Exactly.
Whenever Sha Yue'er has doubts,
she makes her feel understood first.
(Cui Kaiyi is so supportive)
She doesn't just throw advice at her.
She mimicked
how Sha Yue'er
got so excited
yesterday.
She was basically saying,
"Look how silly I was yesterday."
Seeing her act it out
made Sha Yue'er
even happier.
Exactly.
She's really good at playing along.
Her reactions are always spot-on.
She's just
really wise,
so she knows how
to hold space
for someone else's confusion.
(Cui Kaiyi, the perfect listener)
She listens and gives great feedback.
Exactly.
Hey, Liang Xiaoyu.
Your room smells wonderful.
It's the scent
of this Pantene Rose Hair Oil.
I use it every time I wash my hair.
It contains fine-molecule oils.
Look.
It has a lightweight, fluid texture.
It absorbs in three seconds
without feeling greasy.
It leaves your hair smooth and glossy.
Its woody rose fragrance
lasts all day.
What a versatile hair oil.
With its powerful repairing properties
and a long-lasting fragrance,
I'm ordering it right now.
I'll make my room smell like roses, too.
All right.
Who's there?
Cui Yihang.
(Cui Yihang returns to the Signal House)
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
(Looks up)
Hello.
Are you making dinner?
I'm making Eight Treasure tofu.
Eight Treasure tofu?
What can I do to help?
(Looks up)
Could you help me turn it over?
You could chop some vegetables.
Sure. I'll chop some
vegetables.
(Looks over)
I'll chop some vegetables first.
(Flips it himself)
(Purses his lips)
Did you go to work today, too?
(Initiates a conversation)
Yes. I went back to Hebei.
How long does it take you to get home?
About two hours.
So that's four hours round trip?
Yes, four hours round trip.
Then you didn't get much sleep either.
I had to leave early.
So I had to get up early.
What did you guys do here?
You stayed up so late.
We talked about our day.
We do a little review.
No.
You go over everything?
(Asks in return)
We...
Do we review things, Cao Yiheng?
He has no time for you two.
(Seriously)
He only wants to make tofu.
Cao Yiheng.
We don't do a recap
right?
What is there to review?
We're doing just fine.
What's to review?
Yes. We don't review things.
(Completely absorbed in making tofu)
I can only think of Eight Treasure Tofu.
Did you two talk for a while
here?
Yes, we did.
Talk about personal
matters?
Yes.
What personal matters?
Well, those personal
matters can be rather private.
Take a peek.
Is that all right?
Then you tell me yours first.
I don't have any.
I have nothing to share.
Who has something to share?
Is it you or her?
(Follows up)
Her?
Who is she?
Her roommate.
And you're not saying anything.
(Laughs)
We...
I asked you first.
After watching
many episodes, I think
they're sometimes
on the same wavelength.
Very compatible.
Have you tried donkey pastries?
(Donkey meat pastries
brought back by Cui Yihang)
No.
You've never tried them?
I've never had them.
All right.
Try one later.
Sure.
There's one in there
that's rather special.
All right.
He gave Siying
a special donkey meat pastry.
How sweet.
(Checks the recipe notes)
Cui Kaiyi.
Hello.
I'm back.
Cui Kaiyi is so full of energy.
Of course.
(Smiles)
This is...
(Stir-frying)
Cao Yiheng.
We've been waiting for you.
(Walks over to look)
Is it finished?
Not yet.
Look, I've already broken the tofu.
But it smells so good.
What is today's
dish?
Eight Treasure Tofu.
(Eight ingredients paired with the tofu)
There are so many ingredients.
It's almost ready.
Looks like I've got nothing left to do.
It's all right.
I'll just eat, then.
You can just eat.
I'll dish some out.
Why do they sound
so sweet when they talk?
We're only a few episodes in
and we're already seeing this.
Those two just seem
to be naturally drawn to each other,
right?
I'll just eat, then.
You can just eat.
I'll dish some out.
I'll get that for you.
The Children's Day flowers.
There are flowers
for Children's Day, too?
Yes.
I have a gift for you, too.
It's the kind that...
(Jumps)
a miniature bouquet.
Should I put the pot here?
Is that all right?
That's fine.
Let it fry for a while first.
I have a gift for you, too.
I'll go get it for you.
I'll come with you.
I want to exchange gifts.
When your heart is sweet,
even your steps feel lighter.
Watching the two of them,
we see you two
the same way.
You're always together,
so that's the impression
we get.
(Children's Day gifts)
(Laughs)
How are today's flowers
different from yesterday's?
Today's is just a single stem.
It's beautiful.
It feels so special.
I have a gift for you, too.
A little cake
(Exchanging Children's Day gifts)
and some eye drops.
Didn't you say your eyes hurt?
Eye drops.
(Looks)
My eyes are saved.
Not bad.
How cute.
My eyes hurt, too.
My eyes hurt.
Don't shake it.
It's a little cake, right?
Yes. It'll fall apart.
Then should I eat it quickly?
Sure. Otherwise, take it downstairs.
Will it melt?
It might.
All right.
It's been a long time
since I've had a cake.
I only prepared enough for you.
A special preference.
Someone else is back.
(Zhao Xilun returns to the Signal House)
Hello.
Happy Children's Day, everyone.
Happy Children's Day.
Why do I smell something burnt?
I think it's burnt.
It seems so.
(Laughs)
You just had to go upstairs.
Now it's burnt.
(Looks)
(They exchange a smile)
You've gotten this far?
Yes.
I'll be taking an important
step soon.
How do I put this on?
(Helps her put on the apron)
Okay.
Classic apron moment.
You can take the dishes out
and arrange them on a plate.
This is perfect for me.
I'm good at this.
I just lay out the lettuce, right?
Yes.
For aesthetic purposes.
It wasn't exactly well made
to begin with.
You did an excellent job.
I just came in
(Praise)
and could smell the delicious food.
But I didn't plate it very well.
It broke apart a little.
That's all right.
When they're this sweet,
everything tastes good.
But today,
the two of them aren't eating here.
So,
we only have
ten people eating.
(Notices)
What?
Exactly four.
These are for you.
Okay. Thank you.
I just washed them.
Thank you.
Who's not eating?
Chen Hewen and Sha Yue'er
are in the stargazing room.
Stargazing room today?
Didn't they reserve it yesterday?
I think they booked it
yesterday for today.
That's my guess.
Did you actually see them?
(Looks)
I saw them go there.
All right.
Zhao Xilun is lost again.
Lost again.
He doesn't know
what to do.
(Heart Signal Mini Scene)
(30 minutes earlier)
Let me show you around.
Sha Yue'er looks particularly
beautiful today.
Our stargazing room
offers four exclusive packages
(Candlelight and Roses, Summer Breeze)
for them to choose from.
(Blazing Romance, Slow-Cooked Moments)
With an advance reservation,
they can enjoy a private dinner for two.
(Hands over the key)
Open the door.
Take a look around.
Wait. Let me look first.
Let's have a look around.
All right.
You go in first.
Okay.
Want to explore this area,
or look around first?
Let's look at this first.
Okay.
(First floor of stargazing room)
(Second floor of stargazing room)
The vibe is wonderful.
It looks beautiful.
Let's go upstairs.
All right.
The stargazing room
(Private stargazing corner for two)
has a professional
astronomical
telescope.
It's very comfortable.
Yes.
(Professional Astronomical Telescope)
Look. This is very professional.
This really is a wonderful place.
(Enjoying the stars together)
It's rather romantic.
The way they've designed this space...
This place is wonderful.
Let's stargaze
after dinner.
All right.
(Exclusive LEGO rose set for two)
There's also LEGO downstairs.
We can build it together.
Look at this.
You can take a look.
We can take a photo, too.
Yes.
How about we come back after dinner
and take a photo?
Sure.
I'm so hungry.
(Feeling hungry)
I barely ate anything for lunch.
I'm hungry just looking at it
(Private romantic dinner
for two, Candlelight and Roses)
I'll sit?
You sit first.
I'll sit.
Let me move your chair forward a little.
(Helps adjust the chair)
There you go.
That was very gentlemanly.
Everything in romance dramas is real.
Look.
(Looks)
When did you arrive?
A little before you.
Not much earlier.
(Looks down)
He's too shy to look at her.
(Looks)
Go ahead.
Let's start eating.
We're pretty hungry.
Let's eat first.
We can talk while we eat.
All right.
This is quite good.
Let's drink something.
See what you'd like.
You pick first.
Okay, I'll pick first.
Anything you like.
When you walked in,
I noticed that your hair
looked different
from a few days ago.
Does it look good?
There's a bow at the back.
(Shows it)
I saw it.
I just saw it.
It looks good.
Of course.
(Glances)
You look really good in black.
(Compliments)
That look in her eyes.
Give me a smile.
(Teases)
(Smiles with lips pressed)
(Smiles too)
So obedient.
You look really good when you smile.
(Compliments again)
I'm totally won over.
You look really good when you smile.
(Compliments again)
Yeah, and then...
Yeah.
You look great in this outfit today too.
(Compliments)
Thanks.
You know what?
Actually, I...
was really anxious a while back.
About what?
Everyone said I had no jawline.
I seriously wanted to cry.
Let me see.
It is a little hard to find.
Let me see if you have one, babe.
You do.
(Smug)
A little.
Yeah.
You don't get it.
You have to find the right (angle).
Yeah.
I was heavier back then.
Then I lost weight.
Maybe it just takes time.
Do you work out?
I play ball, actually.
I do exercise.
Just not really
going to the gym specifically.
I've been playing
for three or four years.
Have you ever stuck
with any kind of exercise
for a long time?
Pilates.
Did you see
any results?
I think my arms
have some muscle.
I'm sure they do.
Can't tell, though.
At least right now.
You're not flexing,
right?
He's teasing her.
Okay.
I believe you.
When you first saw me,
what did you think?
You turned around
and greeted me through the window.
That really stuck with you?
Of course.
That moment
made me
really want to get to know you.
Yeah, just because you said hi.
And then...
my first impression
was that...
you were really outgoing.
And
you have a great smile.
At the dinner,
you really stood out to me.
Those three words
to describe someone.
I was actually thinking of you.
(I was thinking of you)
That was way too obvious.
Did you hesitate?
I didn't.
(I didn't hesitate)
Actually, I...
already
had the first two words.
I was wondering what
the third one should be.
Then you said
I'm a pretty practical person.
So I thought
okay then.
I'll just go
with practical.
Okay.
Won't that seem too obvious?
Don't you think?
I think it's great.
Pretty bold, actually.
(I think it's great.
Pretty bold, actually)
I picked who I wanted.
I think that's totally normal.
(Sways)
How's work?
I didn't really ask you before.
Like
how long have you
been doing this job?
A few months.
Honestly, I'm still figuring it out.
It's just an internship anyway.
I'm just there to learn.
I think what I'm learning
is pretty useful.
It is.
Well, you're still young.
I'm not much younger than you.
Two years ago, I
probably didn't know
what I wanted either.
You didn't know either?
If I go back two years,
I think
I'd just come back after graduating.
Yeah.
I think everyone feels lost for a while.
Of course.
Have you thought about
starting your own business someday?
Maybe you haven't gotten that far yet,
right?
What made you want to start a business?
(Asks)
Well
I've always had this little dream.
I thought
if someday I could
have my own sports facility,
that'd be...
pretty nice.
It's a little goal of mine.
Yeah, and now
I actually
have my own facility.
It's still being set up, though.
Your parents must
be pretty supportive of you.
It's a little different.
For me,
in my parents' eyes,
it's something
they don't really understand.
But they respect it.
Do you guys
get a lunch break?
Yeah.
That's good.
A while back,
we'd sometimes start a meeting
and go until 2 or 3AM.
(Smiles with lips pressed)
Such a career man.
(Teases)
Chen Hewen's thinking,
I've gotta act more mature.
Sha Yue'er's thinking,
so cute.
What day in April
is your birthday again?
Don't say anything.
The fifth or ninth?
(Waits expectantly)
Cui Yihang's is the ninth.
I remember you're four days apart.
Five days.
(Both go silent)
Yours is the fourth.
Okay.
No, I mean...
Cancers are supposed
to have good memories.
(Nods)
What's your rising sign?
I told you.
Pop quiz time.
Pisces or something?
Whose Pisces is that?
How would I know?
I remember you said it was a water sign.
Cancer,
right?
See?
Pisces and Cancer
are pretty close.
They're both water signs.
At least I
didn't mix up the person.
No.
Right.
I like this part.
I didn't mean to.
It's fine.
Maybe he just stood out to you.
No.
You really stood out to me.
But I don't even know your number.
Honestly.
Why don't you tell me?
I'm July 17.
July 17.
(Memorizing it)
Okay, got it.
From now on,
I think we can
remember some things
about each other.
Sound good?
See? Your memory
is about as bad as mine.
Yeah.
The two of us
put together
could probably
make one whole brain.
(Together, we've got one whole brain)
I just think
we can
take our time.
We've got plenty
of time.
(We've got plenty of time
to take it slow)
That conversation
was perfect.
A little jealous.
That's exactly the vibe.
A little jealousy like this
almost feels like acting cute.
Let's go up and look.
See if we can spot anything.
Have you used a telescope before?
No, this is my first time.
Press confirm,
then...
See anything?
I can see stars.
Really?
I wanna see too.
Come here.
Look.
Right next to the moon.
That's through the telescope.
It's so pretty.
So pretty.
Yeah.
We can put this together.
Okay.
(Welcome to the stargazing room)
Let's look at this.
Let's figure it out.
(Sighs)
Look.
Here.
(Hands it over)
The manual.
(Laughs)
I know it's the manual.
Here.
(Imitating her)
The manual.
Why are you so funny?
Oh no.
Should I be praising you?
Like, wow!
Yeah.
I deserve some praise.
You even found the manual.
Good job, kiddo.
Yeah.
Kiddo?
You even found the manual.
Here.
I think we can sort these.
Like, the matching pieces.
We can pull those out first.
That might make things easier.
Okay.
But...
Is there yellow?
Yeah.
There is.
Of course.
I already saw it.
I just saw it.
I think you're pretty funny too.
Funny? So to you,
is that good or bad?
Hard to say.
You don't like funny people?
I think being funny is good.
But I really feel like
you're the type who's...
(Looks up at him)
Like...
Like what?
What?
Experienced.
You mean in relationships?
You think I'm that experienced?
Because I feel like
you're way too smooth.
But I'm really
not that kind of person.
(Looks straight at her)
But you're curious
why I'm like this?
Because you just seem
like that kind of person.
So being smooth
is suddenly
a bad thing now?
No.
Then next time I should...
It's a good thing.
It's good to speak your mind.
You've got a mouth.
Why have one if you don't use it,
right?
But I still
have some doubts.
If you've got doubts,
then I think
you should
really
get to know the real me.
(If you have doubts about me,
get to know the real me)
He's really sincere.
So where were we?
Then we put the yellow piece
in here.
Then we're...
I think we're good.
Isn't it red?
Red was the last step.
Got it.
Sorry.
I look so dumb.
I don't think so.
(Humming)
That sounds nice.
♪Living an ordinary life♪
Is that how it goes?
♪I wonder if I'll ever♪
♪Find a love sweet as honey♪
Teresa Teng.
Hasn't he sung that twice now?
Yeah.
He sang it in the bathroom too.
He's so funny!
Building a pink LEGO bouquet
in the stargazing room
feels pretty romantic.
Yeah.
You're really good at this.
Do you build LEGO a lot?
When I was little,
I'd build them with my brother.
When I'm building,
I get really absorbed in it.
Yours looks so good.
You're pretty good at it too.
Putting it together piece by piece
makes time feel slower.
Right?
Let's put the flowers
in the vase together.
Sure.
(Welcome to the stargazing room)
I think
a relationship
is kind of like LEGO.
You build it piece by piece
and get to know each other slowly.
That's how you grow closer.
(Exactly)
These two
seem really in sync now.
Wanna take a picture?
Sure.
We can take a Star Baby.
There's also a photo wall.
Since we're the first ones here,
we can put ours up.
Yeah.
We should leave our photo here,
right?
Yeah.
Are...
Are you taking it, or...
(Asking)
They have to take one together.
Should we take photos of each other,
or just hold it together?
Together, right?
I've never done this.
Then come sit over here.
(Inviting)
I can come over.
(Quickly stands up)
We can each hold one
for the photo.
And then...
Yeah.
(Smiles)
One each.
(Hesitates)
No, I think
(Sitting side by side)
you can take one from your angle.
Then we can put up two photos.
(Suddenly very chatty)
Don't you think it's kind of...
Chen Hewen's blushing.
Pretty fun?
Okay.
Come on.
Move over that way a bit.
Okay.
I got you in the shot.
You...
Chen Hewen.
Chen Hewen's ears
are pinker than the flowers.
Is this right?
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
How about this?
This way, we're even in the frame.
No.
Then I need to sit farther back.
(Moves even closer)
You stay on the left.
I'll squeeze in on the right.
Three.
Two.
One.
I think...
I think this one should...
Look pretty good.
I think it's perfect.
Perfect.
Sha Yue'er
likes this kind of enthusiasm.
She likes people who are direct.
She likes things to be clear.
Zeng, what do you like
about Zhang Jin?
One thing I've
always liked about Zhang Jin
is
she's
always been really sincere
and genuine.
And she gives me
this kind of...
lively feeling.
And I feel like I've always
been trying, as the two of us
spend time together,
to be someone who can
help her or protect her.
I want to keep doing that.
Just protect her
and let her stay true to herself.
Yeah, stay true to herself.
Yeah.
You've never told me any of this.
(So sweet)
I'm kind of touched.
I'm shipping them now.
So sweet.
We're shipping them in here
and out there too.
With Zeng Zhaohao,
I'm more drawn
to his temperament
and personality.
What's his temperament like?
Steady.
He can really handle
all my emotions.
Does he look good in black?
He looks amazing.
This dark-colored look.
Isn't this
what people online
are calling
(Simple, polished, mature, reliable)
the "husband material" look?
I think he
kind of has that vibe.
I should've worn black too.
Yours...
I look like a flowerpot.
Curtains.
(Curtain buddies)
We're both curtains.
(Sun Qimeng returns to the Signal House)
Hi, guys.
What are you doing?
Hi.
There's so much food today.
You're so pretty today.
I got everyone Children's Day gifts.
One tulip each.
Applause! I love it!
Cui Kaiyi is definitely
(Maximum emotional support)
someone who hypes everything up.
Another meme reaction.
Applause! I love it!
That's so thoughtful.
(Laughs)
Yeah.
One each.
They're orange.
So pretty.
Yeah.
They're really pretty.
You can pick one.
So pretty.
(Glances)
What are you making?
This is Eight Treasure tofu.
Si and Cui Yihang
have so much food over there.
Meng, try this.
This one's done.
(Walks over to Zhao Xilun)
You guys have a feast here.
It feels like Chinese New Year.
(Glances back)
She keeps looking at Zhao Xilun.
Are you making a sauce?
Yeah.
I'm making dipping sauce.
Dipping sauce.
And the meat
will probably need to stew for a while.
That works.
Then we'll roast it
with the broccoli later.
(Stands behind him watching)
Meng is always
following Zhao Xilun around.
(Walks back to his side)
Whip up a dipping sauce.
That's impressive.
Do you need me
to help with anything?
Actually,
this pot just
keeps cooking on its own.
On its own.
You can just watch it
quietly.
Just quietly enjoy it.
Okay.
I'll quietly watch it.
I'm "dying" laughing.
He's looking lively today.
Today's good.
Got his energy back.
Yeah.
You got this.
(Looks toward the stargazing room)
One hand in the pocket today.
(Fully switched on)
And he styled his hair.
Yeah!
Hi.
Hi, guys.
Hey, guys.
What time did you get here?
We...
just got here too.
Why's everyone here so early?
Did you eat?
I ate
just a little.
Add a little MSG.
Who still isn't back?
There's...
One, two, three.
Chen Hewen,
Sha Yue'er,
and who else?
Chen Hewen, Sha Yue'er,
and Liang Xiaoyu.
None of them are back yet?
(Glances)
Exchanging glances.
I don't know.
Chen Hewen and Sha Yue'er
should be
in the stargazing room.
Seriously?
When you came over, did you see
if the lights were on over there?
(Asking)
Zhao Xilun
knows everything
I saw the lights on.
I just didn't know they were inside.
Didn't he use that
stargazing room card yesterday?
Who used the stargazing card?
Chen Hewen used it yesterday.
That's wild.
(Rubs hands)
Now I really
wanna go peek.
And yesterday, outside,
the sky was...
(Presses lips)
That projection
made it look like a sky
full of stars.
Really?
It was outside,
in the garden.
Only Qimeng knows
what actually happened.
Yeah.
She was too busy admiring
Zhao Xilun.
(Only has eyes for him)
She can't see anyone else now.
Only Zhao Xilun.
Yep.
How did you guys see it?
You just happened
to stumble across it?
I think...
Lun told me about it.
He somehow became the gossip himself.
Yeah.
Yeah, it projected the lights
onto the trees.
She's stunned.
Onto the trees?
Yeah. It was gorgeous.
Now I really wanna sneak a peek,
but that'd be kinda rude, right?
Yeah. When I got here,
I saw the lights on inside.
You saw it lit up inside.
(Glances)
Meng keeps watching
Zhao Xilun's reaction.
I thought...
I thought the lights in there
were always on.
I didn't notice.
I don't think so.
When we went to look that day,
it was still dark.
This is so fun.
Let's grab our Star Babies.
Okay.
I'll take the one on the right.
Let's sit for a bit.
Sit for a bit.
Over here.
Come sit over here.
Anything you wanna say?
Anything you wanna ask?
Go ahead.
(Chen Hewen)
Ask me anything.
Then...
your ideal type.
I think you've mentioned it before.
You talked about it yesterday too.
You said you might like someone
a little more reserved, right?
That's basically
what you said yesterday.
Actually, not anymore.
I've realized
I really need reassurance.
So maybe someone more direct
(Sha Yue'er)
would make me feel more secure.
If they're too reserved,
I might feel like
I can't read them.
(Smiles)
I feel like you and I
are alike in so many ways.
Really?
Yeah.
And
I actually
really value
security
and emotional support.
I think
emotional support
should go both ways.
As for security,
I guess
I didn't
get much of that
from my family.
And
it might have to do
with my childhood.
Why didn't you feel secure
with your family?
(Follows up)
It goes back to my childhood.
When I was little,
I went a long time
without seeing my parents.
My grandparents raised me.
Were your parents
busy working?
Yeah.
Back then, because of that,
I remember crying a lot.
And because of it,
I'd act out a lot.
But honestly,
my grandparents treated me really well.
Looking back now,
I feel like
you can't always
have everything.
I think maybe
they were
working their hardest
because they wanted
to give me a better
life.
So I can't just look at it
from my own perspective
and blame them.
I don't think anyone was wrong.
I just feel like
when I was growing up,
the love from my grandparents
and the love from my parents
just weren't quite the same.
Yeah.
They're different.
I think security
matters so much to me
because
I want
something
that's
long-term and stable.
Yeah.
Like,
I'd be willing
to change for you,
and you'd be willing
to change for me.
I think we could both grow
into better people.
I think that's probably
what a good relationship is about.
Yeah.
I feel like we're pretty lucky to meet.
But out of all
the people I've met here,
I think
you gave me
the best first impression.
(Smiles)
After comparing everyone?
Well,
everyone compares.
Don't you compare me
to Zhao Xilun?
These two are getting competitive.
That's pretty savage.
There you go.
Being snarky again!
If you're gonna ask me that,
you should've known
I'd answer like that.
Wouldn't you?
My friend,
maybe think about
what you did
the day before yesterday.
I apologized for that.
I know I messed up.
And you're still giving me attitude?
I...
shouldn't.
But I'm just saying,
I think comparing people is normal.
To me,
you should compare.
You're pretty honest.
Everyone has the right
to choose who's a better fit.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
Those two are kinda going head-to-head.
Yeah, they really are.
But they're talking really well.
Neither one's making it
awkward for the other.
It's really interesting.
So do you think
when someone makes the first move,
like,
does that put pressure on you?
(Thinking)
If it's someone
I'm not interested in,
then yeah, it's pretty stressful.
Do you think our conversation today
has been
pretty easy
and relaxed?
So what do you think
overall?
Like,
after yesterday and today,
what do you think of me?
I think you're great.
Yeah.
I even brought these
mosquito-repellent wristbands.
Here's one for you.
Thanks.
Wear two.
- Put one on your other wrist too.
- Okay.
Maybe that'll work better.
One on each wrist.
Okay.
I'll put your favorite blue one on you.
Thanks.
Any color you like?
Blue.
You remembered.
The kind of guy
who quietly takes care of things.
(Looks closely)
Yesterday, I think
your face turned red.
My face wasn't just red.
It was burning up.
Really?
You know, you...
(Covers face)
When I said something?
It's not when you said something.
You have this...
this look you give people.
You know?
What kind of look?
You sit up really straight,
(Imitates her)
then tilt your head down like this,
and give them this
really intense stare.
You...
You haven't noticed
you do that?
I haven't.
But I think that's
part of your charm too.
I think it's just...
I just get shy.
This back-and-forth...
They're being so direct,
but still playing this back-and-forth.
These two
are kind of...
Every time it's,
"What do you think"?
"Well, what do you think"?
Neither one gives too much
away too easily.
They still test the waters.
(Stares)
I feel like you're
avoiding my eyes a little now.
I like this pace.
Yeah, when I get shy,
yeah,
I probably do
a little.
(Looks straight at her)
(Can't help smiling)
Yeah, but I think
my impression of you,
like what I can see,
is only
what's on the surface.
Yeah.
But I think I'd rather
get to know
you,
the whole you.
That's why
yesterday,
I worked up some courage.
(I worked up the courage because I
wanted to know more about you)
This date...
My dear friends,
my heart's pounding watching this.
Having this time alone
is
so precious.
See how important
the stargazing room is?
That thing Sha Yue'er did
was iconic.
"Give me a smile".
Sha Yue'er's
really comfortable
(Cupid, Fiona Sit)
looking him right in the eyes.
She barely looks away.
That kind of stare,
if someone looked at me like that,
I'd get nervous.
Sha Yue'er really likes
seeing him get nervous.
She thinks...
Yeah!
It's super cute.
Yeah.
The more nervous he gets,
the more she stares at him.
As girls,
what's
the psychology behind that?
It's that
unexpected contrast.
It's cute.
You can really tell
this time,
when she had dinner with Chen Hewen,
she was
clearly much more
curious about him.
(Actively getting to know him)
She asked
a lot of questions.
And between them,
there's more
shyness too.
Because they took
those little
points of friction
and talked about them so directly.
(Straight talk)
"You don't know what you did"?
All that comes through
is this
feeling of mutual interest.
They've definitely
taken a huge step forward.
And their whole conversation
was
this constant
back-and-forth.
You come at me, right?
I'll come right back!
(Back and forth)
They're all about that push and pull.
They're testing each other.
Didn't they say
they're both
people who need reassurance?
So they always want the other person
to say it first,
then they'll respond.
They've got
a different
kind of push and pull.
You know?
Like fire and water.
They're always butting heads.
Both of them
seem like they want
(Taking the lead)
the upper hand.
Right.
Lucky,
you two have been through this before.
Share your experience.
I feel like we
weren't really
the back-and-forth type.
We were more like
the "senior version".
(Senior version)
I think.
Back then, we'd just
pull weeds
and plant flowers.
The two of us were
a little too chill.
You were chill?
You were anything but.
Really?
You were holding his invitation card
and doing what?
Here.
(We've got a longtime viewer here)
(Is that me?)
Zeng nervously
takes a tactical sip of tea.
(Don't go anywhere. The next episode
is even more romantic.)